所以死者才会沸腾
Well, that explains why the victims boiled.
用量越大  热量就越大
The higher the dose, the higher the heat.
也许它就是被设计成这样
Maybe it was designed that way.
根据尸检报告
According to the M.E. report,
[中枢神经兴奋剂  即冰毒]
迷幻药中被掺入了大量的脱氧麻黄碱
the ecstasy was cut with a high volume of methamphetamine.
来见证奇迹吧
Go for greatness.
亲爱的
Hey, baby girl.
我需要你帮我查下会延迟发作的MDMA
I need you to run a search on delayed onset MDMA.
脱氧麻黄碱混合物
Methamphetamine mixtures.
看你能不能找到些
See if you can find anything about--
-我的天  -怎么了
- Whoa. - What?
我的娘亲的奶奶的老祖宗啊
Double oh to the whoa to the oh whoa power.
有一种毒品叫什么副甲基之类的
There's a drug called para-methox...ish...
副甲氧基甲基安非他命吗
Para-methoxymethamphetamine?
对  就是你刚才说的  缩写为PMMA
Yes. What you just said. PMMA for short.
刚在国际市场上市
It just hit the international market.
它的别名是死亡博士  这可不是我取的
Its street name, which I'm not making up, is doctor death.